tanjung.info 2012-12-10

# Privacy - Tanjung Info

Collection of personal information  
Personal information on this Site is collected by Tanjung.info.  
Tanjung.info will not send you any email regarding other products, services, or special offers, although we may communicate with you regarding your use of the services on this Site. Tanjung.info will not provide your personal information to other companies or organizations without your consent.   
How personal information is used  
Tanjung.info collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you subscribe to a service, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users.   
Tanjung.info may collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected without identifying any user individually. Tanjung.info may use this non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes. 

Service announcements  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send all registered users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, but they are not promotional in nature. 

Protection of your personal information  
The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of Tanjung.info services is classified as Registration Information. Registration Information is protected in several ways. Access by you to your Registration Information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone.   
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, for example in a chat room, that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Links to other sites  
This Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Tanjung.info is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Use of cookies  
When you visit this Site, you can browse the Site and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our Site, we may use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you.   
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. (For some Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.) 

Log files  
In addition to standard server log files, this site generates its own log files. These log files provide usernames, date/time stamp, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, platform type, and other statistical information. None of the information in Tanjung.info log files is linked to personally identifiable information. 

Changes in privacy policy  
All "personal information" ("personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. Tanjung.info reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the homepage of the Site for thirty (30) days.
